12 axis quids reveals political
alignments with conservatism to ten to
to technocracy.
Okay.
All right.
Sure.
I'll take the quiz right now. Let's go.
Uh 60. I'll do 60. All right.
Serious situation. The government should
be allowed to impose a curfew. Strongly
agree. Minimum wage should not be set
too high because that reduces jobs. Uh
neutral. Uh peace only exists when the
enemy knows the response to an attack
will be devastating. Strongly agree. In
serious crisis, a strong leader should
be able to govern without depending
depending on legislature. Strongly
agree. Each state should a province
should be feel free to draft its own
constitution without interference of
national government. Uh I I disagree but
not strongly. Um my country should
pressure neighboring governments that
threaten its century.
I don't think it should pressure. I
think there's there's like one that's
even above that. Um, uh, public officers
should be Oh, let me move it and and
zoom in you. That way you guys can see.
Uh, public officers can be filled with
randomly selected citizens as juries are
rather than election. That's
Uh, when the law of man contradicts the
law of God, the law of God comes first.
I I think it really depends. Actually, I
disagree with this. I generally
disagree. Open relationships and uh
polyamory or choices as legitimate as
traditional marriage. Uh, I I agree, but
I don't think they're as legitimate.
Like I I I I think actually I'm neutral
on this. I'm neutral on this. No, I'm g
I'm giving you my answer. I'm giving you
my answer, not what other people think.
This is my answer. So, I'm neutral.
Yeah, it depends. Uh, adults should be
allowed to keep firearms. Strongly
agree. No country has the right to
change another country's government.
Strongly disagree. Uh, we can do
whatever we want. We could do whatever
we any anytime that we can, then we have
the right to do it. No political or
ideological cause justifies starting a
war. Strongly disagree. Indigenous and
traditional communities should be able
to live under their own rules within
their own territory. Strongly disagree.
What if they want to rape each other? We
can't let that happen. Especially
whenever they exist inside of a larger
system that we need to use in order to
take care of them. Uh coexistence of
different languages and cultures should
be encouraged in a country. Strongly
disagree. Um, you know, again, what do
you you want to go and read signs?
They're in another language.
no. Obviously not. The state should
be allowed to monitor digital
conversations to prevent and combat
crime. It depends. Obviously, it depends
on a warrant very clearly. Collecting
taxes and in the end is a form of theft.
I strongly strongly disagree with this.
Um, uh, theft implies ownership.
Ownership is defined by the state to the
the fact the state that can redefine if
you own what you have. Uh, ownership is
not a con. Ownership is a construct. So
uh yeah that's it. Uh so I I don't agree
with that at all. The word God should
not appear in the constitution of
political speeches. Strongly disagree.
God is fundamental to America. America
is a Christian country. It was founded
on Christian ideals and western culture
is Roman law. Greek philosophy and
Christian morality. Uh religion
strengthens the community life and
should be encouraged. I agree but not
strongly. Um cheap Chinese electric cars
should pay tariffs to protect local
factories. I strongly agree with this as
well. uh voluntary euthanasis should be
legalized for people suffering from
terminal illnesses. I strongly agree
with this too. I think if you want to
kill yourself, you should be able to. My
grandfather, great-grandfather killed
himself. And uh you know, some people in
the family are like, "Oh, this is a bad
thing." My dad's like, "This is this was
this was a good thing. This is a good
thing he killed himself because he was
wasting all the family's money. He knew
he was going to die. He just jumped out
the window." That's what it was.
Yeah.
Jumped out the window.
Whatever happened to falling on your
sword?
Whatever happened to that?
Really? Like it it people are such
nowadays. It's embarrassing.
We're all dying though. Yes. And uh uh
even a government elected by a huge
majority must respect the rights of of
the opposition. Nope. Um a pesticide
should be used. And yeah, obviously not
not it depends on what the rights are.
Actually, let me go back. I'm going to
do neutral. It dep I'm going to do it
depends, right? Because I don't always
agree with that, but I don't I don't
always disagree with that. Pesticides
should be reduced even if that lowers
agricultural productivity. Uh I don't
have I don't I'm neutral on that. I
don't care. Strategic supply chains such
as medicines, chips should be protected
from foreign competition. Uh it depends.
I think it really does depend.
Immigrants should not have to abandon
their customs to live well in a country.
I strongly disagree. You either
assimilate or get the out. uh even
in the face of a genocide in a
neighboring country, my country should
not get involved militarily. I think it
depends obviously. Um in a multicultural
society should live with several
languages in everyday life. I strongly
disagree. If you can't speak English,
get out of the country. Uh and uh what's
this here? A government should be able
to control the exchange rate to protect
an actual economy. Yeah, obviously they
should be able to control the economy.
Like duh. Um uh the world would be
better off without economic borders
working as a single global market. Uh I
disagree with this. Not massively
because I do believe in some degree of
global trade, but I also don't think
that it should be 100% that way. And uh
pesticides are why your hair is falling
out. That's right. Um that's that's
exactly the reason why. That's why all
those uh those monks from back in the
day um they uh they they had they had
they were bald. It's because of that.
Espionage and covert military operations
are legitimate tools of state. Strongly
agree. Genderneutral language should not
be adopted by society. Strongly agree.
the government should limit imports that
threaten local industry and jobs. I
think it depends. Uh pressuring other
countries is legitimate when national
interest is at stake. It's not I don't
agree that it's necessary. Um mining
should be allowed even in areas of
preserved areas of the rainforest. Uh I
strongly disagree with this. Uh I think
that we need to preserve our natural
environment and we can find other places
to mine rocks in. Uh the only place to
mine rocks are not the only preserved
areas in the world. Like I I really Yes.
I I I'm a I'm a nature conservationist.
I know. I know. You might not want to
hear it. We can find other places. The
state should avoid new regulations on
economic activity. It depends. Um
immigrants who reject local customs
should lose the right to remain the
country. Strongly agree. Spending on
space exploration should take lower
priority than environmental protections
on Earth. I disagree, but not strongly.
It depends on what the scope is because
space exploration has given us things
like Velcro and other levels of
technological improvements that we use
in our everyday life. So I think that
space exploration is fundamentally
science and as science develops space
exploration will also help us in America
as well, right? It depends. Space is so
I' I'd say I' disagree. Fundamentally I
disagree. Um genetically modified crops
should continue to be developed.
Strongly agree. Obviously regional and
local lenders should carry out central
government decisions on local matters.
Um well yeah obviously they should cover
out the decisions like yeah duh. I mean
of course like I mean I I guess I agree
like what regional and local leaders
I think it depends. It dep No. No. I'm
going to go back and say it depends
right because I don't want to have like
for example like them saying like oh we
don't want ICE in our country and our in
our our city. I don't think they should
be able to say no, right? So it's hard
really for me to know how to answer that
properly.
Religion is a personal matter and should
not influence influence public policy. I
disagree not strongly but I do disagree.
I think it depends on the religion. I
want Christianity influencing American
policy. I don't want Hinduism, Islam or
Judaism influencing American policy.
This is a Christian country and it
should be for Christian people and it
should be based off of the Christian
morality. So I have a tier list for it.
So like my actual my actual option isn't
even on the list. Real marriage is
between a man and a woman. I strongly
disagree with this. I think this is
ridiculous. I think if you want to get
married to a guy, it's completely
legitimate. Uh it's not the same as a
religious marriage, but to the extent
that a state accepts a marriage as
anything, everybody should be treated
the same regardless of what their gender
is. Uh a revolution might be necessary
to take economic power out of the hands
of the few. Uh I think it really
depends. Um experts selected for their
qualifications should govern without
being elected by the public. I think it
also depends. Um, a a country should
refuse entry demigrants who reject local
customs. Strongly agree. And let's see
here. Uprising and chat. Hey guys. Guys,
I'm knocking these out.
We're speedrunning this.
This is the way it is. You are indeed.
Yes. Constitutional god. Yeah, bro.
Like, I'm telling you like this. This is
the way I think.
Isn't real marriage uh part of
Christianity, which would create a
conflict between two of your opinions?
Well, uh that's not how I define real
marriage. I define real marriage in the
way that a state defines real marriage.
A religious marriage isn't real because
I don't believe in religion.
I don't believe in religion, but I think
other people should believe in religion.
I understand that you might think that
these ideas are contradictory, but they
are not. Uh I am not a Christian. I do
not believe in God, but I am culturally
Christian and I want to live in a
Christian country.
Does that make sense?
It's extremely reasonable. Think about
the kids. Yes, it understands the
morality of religion. Yes, religious
faith is part of the part of the It
depends on what the faith is. Strongly
agree. In serious crisis, the government
should be able to freeze rents. Uh, I
think it I'm either agree or it depends.
Um, I agree. I I I do agree. Uh, I
prefer an authoritarian regime to
democracy if it accelerated my country's
development. I agree. I I think it
depends.
Uh,
authoritarian regime to democracy if it
accelerated my country's development.
Um
well I do you know I I would say I agree
and here's why because I don't believe
in democracy to be I think I well I do
believe in democracy just not for
everybody. Uh companies should be
considered strategically important and
should remain under public control. I
think it depends right. You have some
companies that obviously should things
like, for example, a a uh electric
company that is in an area and there's
only one electric company in the area
because it operates as a monopoly. It
needs to have public control because if
it doesn't, then it could just start
charging people tons of money and cause
huge problems. I think this one really
does depend, right? A United Nations
should not should be able to mediate
conflicts before any med military
action. No, the America should uh
regional and local government should not
uh have any should have the autonomy to
decide their own affairs without relying
on national government. I strongly
disagree. We fought a war over it.
Family inheritance should be protection
from policies that redistribute wealth.
I think it depends. I I agree. I I agree
with some level of taxes, but not a huge
level of taxes. I think that you need to
have taxes. I I I'm relatively neutral
on this. Yeah, I'm I'm neutral. Like,
I'm I'm a big fan of taxes.
People might not want to hear that. We
need taxes.
Sorry, I'm rational.
Yeah, taxes are horrible. Okay, well
then you can't have a go. You can't have
a country. You have to have taxes.
You have to have taxation theft. No,
it's not. Theft implies ownership.
Ownership is defined by the state. To
the extent that the state can define
ownership, the state can also define
theft because it defines ownership. So
if the state takes something away from
you, they didn't steal it from you
because you never owned it to begin with
because they were the ones that defined
whether you owned it.
Ownership is not real. You don't own
anything.
If somebody can take it away from you,
it's not yours, is it?
That's dumb. That's the natural law of
existence.
Do you want to know why we own Texas?
It's because we killed everybody that
was fighting for it and we beat Mexico.
That's why it's pretty simple.
Why is it called the United States and
not England? It's cuz we won a
revolutionary war. There's no ownership.
Ownership is fake.
I'm neutral.
When a market excludes the poor, the
state should take over the service
directly. Uh, it depends. Uh, an
independent central bank is worth more
than the current government's political
wishes. Uh, it depends. Teenagers should
learn about sexuality and gender without
taboos. Um, this is going to be a
controversial topic.
I'm either neutral to agree on this.
I am I'm either neutral to agree. This
is going to be this is going to be a
dividing one.
not from the state.
Like I like basically I think that like
because like teenagers a like 17 and 13
are really different, right?
I think it I think this is really it
depends because like so gender should
matter but like there there's only two
genders, right? So like I don't know
really what the context of this question
is. I'm going to be I'm going to say it
depends. This is too broad.
Regional taxes should follow national
laws to prevent tax disputes between
regions. It depends. Uh drones and
autonomous vehicles provide the decisive
advantage in my country should Wait, who
the wouldn't be Who the would
be against drones?
What kind of a caveman would be against
drones?
What?
Some people are
my country should pursue free trade
agreements with other countries. It
depends. Vaccination should be mandatory
even against those who who refuse. It
depends, right? Things like polio. I
think maybe you could make an argument
for I I would it's either neutral or
disagree.
Uh
cuz like a vaccine like like we're
talking about like a polio vaccine
versus the COVID vaccine. This is apples
and oranges to me or whooping cough.
No, I feel like Yeah, like black plague
I think it really depends on what
the vaccination is, right?
Humanity would live better with less
technology and a simpler and more
natural way of life. I'm neutral to
this. I think Ted I think old Ted Ted
Kazinski was right about a lot of this,
but I think that it's also reductive to
some people that have I think it it
depends.
I'm going to go with it depends.
Racebased quotas are still need
disagree.
Okay. Uh that's what are we talking
about? I don't think so. My country
should be willing to use military force
to protect its interests uh in the
region. Yes. What should society rest
on?
Um
faith, family and national tradition,
custom faith and changing slowly. Live
and let live equality diversion uh
diversity uh tradition order without
religion. Faith and service of social
justice
faith, family and national tradition.
How should power be organized?
Democracy with checks and elites decide
with limited voting. A single leader. I
think elites to side with limited voting
cuz I I don't want to have the thing is
like I would never want to allow a goyam
to be able to affect the voting uh like
any any sort of voting, right? You like
nobody wants goyam voting.
A manag Yeah. This is a managed
democracy. And by the way, do you know
who agreed with this? The founding
fathers of the United States
Constitution.
Who should control production? Uh, it
depends. uh collective uh uh planned
production, no bosses, co-ops, welfare
state, markets with rules in a safety
net, bosses and unions united by the
state, national farms shielded by the
state, free trade and minimal taxes. I
think I think C. I feel like C like
definitely C. Markets with rules and a
safety net. Like duh. I feel like this
is the obvious one, right? How should a
country act abroad?
Uh an influential military power, strong
defense and close allies, diplomacy
before force, armed but out of others
wars, peaceful and non-intervention as
always. Uh an influential military
power.
What role should technology play?
Technology and industry is one
accelerate technology. No brakes.
No brakes.
You're not getting off this train.
We're speedr runninging the singularity
today.
Do you follow a religion?
No. All right.
Oh boy. This is the last question.
Oh man.
Oh man. I'm I'm I'm worried.
Oh boy. What's it going to be? You guys
ready?
Do I follow? No, it says, "Do I follow a
religion?" I do not follow a religion.
You follow the morality of Christianity?
Not always. It depends on the situation.
Uh, yeah. I
Okay, imagine a computer crashes. All
right.
There's no
No way.
Turkey.
No way. Oh god. I don't I'm so afraid to
click on historical. Bro, I'm so Please,
please, please.
Oh, God.
Oh Jesus, bro. Like,
oh man. I
said second, right? Not the third. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Wow. Um,
so let's read what my political opinion
is.
A doctrine coined by uh Germe Fay that
fuses archaic hierarchical
traditionalist values, ethnic identity,
spirituality, and a warrior ethos with
an unreserved embrace of advanced
technology. Arguing that an approaching
civilizational collapse will force
humanity combined tribal social order
with hyper modern science. Compatibility
indicates how close your answers are to
this profile. 92%
92%
match.
Wow. A sentence that describes you. I
want a tribal hierarchical order reborn
from collapse. Fusing archaic traditions
with hyper modern science and
unrestricted techn
Man,
man, I uh
I uh Yeah, that's about right.
That is about right. Uh
interventionists. Oh my god. Power,
security, and liberty. So structure. So
these are the percentage for axes. Let
me go through this. You guys can look at
it all. And you said you are a moderate.
I am. I'm a very moderate guy. I'm an
extremely moderate guy. This is just the
reasonable way of doing things.
Redo it, but take your time.
Why? This is That's what I think.
Yeah, I'm extremely moderate.
Would you prefer if it matched with the
US flag? I I don't really I never even
considered that.
Yeah, I never even considered that at
all.
Assimilation only 97%.
Well, I think people can come in and,
you know, like if they can, you know,
get their together, it's okay,
right? Literally, the imperial of
imperium of 40k.
What sets you apart? Diplomacy. Your
most unusual position. You lean further
towards militarists than 99% of the
ideologies that Yeah, that's because we
have nuclear bombs.
Like, did you know this? We literally
have nuclear bombs. Like, what do you
Are are you
Didn't you know this?
Holy
The second Reich was authoritarian
constitutional mon. You know what? Let's
not talk. Oh, God. We're going to read
We'll read it. We'll read it. You know
what? At this point, it's cooked anyway.
Let's No, no, no, no. We're going to go
all the way. It's fine. Uh, your most
typical position, your position on the
economy sits almost exactly in the
catalog median, right? Of course. And
uh, oh my god. So, and so Turkey is a
presidential republic between Europe and
Asia. Turkey combines electoral
democracy with a strong concentration of
power, nationalism, and religious
conservatism and an assertive foreign
policy in the Middle East and the
Mediterranean. I am a 90% match with
Turkey.
Wait,
99 with
Oh my
Oh my god.
Historically. Okay. All right. Let's
Oh, Jesus Christ. Oh god. Oh boy.
The German Imperial State from 1818
60 uh sorry 71 from 1918
united Prussian le federalism limited
constitutional monarchy male suffrage
uh for the richag a strong Kaiser and
chancer authority rapid
industrialization militarism and a
foreign policy of a rising hour.
You know, I'm German, by the way.
It's crazy, huh?
Wow.
My dad got me one of the little hats
with the spike on it. He did.
Uh, I was a kid. And so, further this
from you, uh, Catalonia, Paris.
Yep.
Yep. That's about right.
Yeah.
I I think I think this makes a lot of
sense.
Mhm.
I've been trying to tell you guys this.
I have been.
Wow.
Um
Oh, man. A Roman general and statesman,
Caesar combined military prestige,
political popular reforms and
concentration of personal authority,
weakening the aristocratic republic, and
paving the way for imperial power in
Rome. Man, what a what a G. Uh, also
closest to you by by dimension and
profile, uh, George Wilheim, Frederick
Eagle, Otto von Bis. There he is. Oh my
god. Furthest from you, Benjamin Tucker.
These are I don't even know who the
these losers are. So overall
compatibility. All right. Let's see.
Julius Caesar. Uh Hegel as well. Uh I
don't Islamist theorist.
Hey. All right.
Theodore Roosevelt.
Jeremy Fay. Look at this here. Oh my. I
don't even know the two two the head of
Dagisan. Two three years in Dagisan.
Oh my god. in the field.
Wow.
Steve Bannon that maybe Colani.
Oh
Oh bro.
Is this the guy who I think it is?
Yeah.
Um
I just really uh
Yeah. Wow. That's crazy, isn't it?
That's really crazy. Further reading. Uh
yeah. Other matches. So these are the
other matches that are ideological pro
ideological proximity. Uh imperialism,
militarism, right-wing populism. the uh
ideology furthest from you, progressive
libertarianism.
Yeah. You know how I learned that
progressive libertarianism was
is I played a video game with no rules.
Yeah. I was like, "Wow, this doesn't
work. This is a hole."
Yeah, this is this doesn't work at all.
What do you mean? Holy
One of my buddies messes me. is
I don't know if I can pronounce it.
Assalamu allayikum my Muslim brother.
When are we going
to Turkey?
I was actually going to go to Turkey
with one some of my friends like maybe a
to meet some guys that that we
knew over there like 3 months ago and
yeah. Wow. It turns out that's crazy,
isn't it?
Uh yeah. Wow. No, we're the good
Muslims. I I'm a big fan of Turkey. I
think Erdogon's an I do. I
think Erdogon's a huge Uh I I
don't like how he runs things and uh I
don't like what he did with the uh with
his uh his political opponents. But, you
know, other than that, I I I respect I
think Turkeyy's a great country, you
know, really. I mean, it is. It is. It's
a great country. So, I don't know what
Yeah. I mean, GG can't go there anymore.
I mean, I don't know. Like I mean if if
he can't handle that, it is what it is.
Yeah. Did you do the 60 questions? Uh I
did. I did 60 questions and I thought
this was the the fair amount. Oh my god.
So
I mean this guy's this is exactly this
is exactly what I wanted it to be.
This is You know what? I'm really I'm
really feeling cute. I'm feeling really
good. Turkey used to be Christian. Yeah.
Until the Muslims took over. That's what
happened.
Yeah. Didn't they it? Yeah. They
didn't that they Yeah. That's what
happened. Like that's history. Yeah.
Until they came and got and got the
place and they said, "No, you're not
going to do that anymore here. It's
the way it is." Miss by one Reich. I No,
no, I didn't miss. I hit.
I It was not a miss.
Why don't you just stop? All right.
Constantinople became a ston. Yeah. And
that's what happens. Listen, listen. We
have America now. We have America.
That's what happens. Except they did a
genocide.
Yeah. Do you know how many of
Genghaskhan?
Yes. It's I'm not defending this by the
way. Abs. It was horrible that it
happened. But like, how the do you
think everything happened in the past?
It's people mass killing each other.
Duh. What the hell did you expect? You
thought everybody just got along?
Holy Well, anyway, guys, um
Wow.
I really don't even know what to say.
That's crazy,
bro. I'm going to be honest. The moment
that I saw the German Empire, I was just
like, "Oh no, bro." Like, that's that's
the clip. That's the clip. Oh, no.
That's the clip. I didn't even read any
other word other than German empire and
I just immediately clicked away. I was
like, "No, fuck." Right? Are we
converting, brother? I mean, listen, I I
I I'm not a converter, but I'm a
respector. I'm a respector. I go to
another country, you know what I'm going
to do if I go to Turkey? I'm going to
respect all of their national customs.
I'm going to hopefully maybe go to one
of their maybe they'll let me visit a
mosque. I can appreciate it and you know
see how cool it is and you know meet
with people and have a good time.
Yeah. Uh that's that that's that's what
you do. You know what they say.
Win in Rome.
Win in Rome. Get Yep. Get some schwarma.
Exactly. And and you know what I want
them to do when they come here? I want
them to come and and and be Americans. I
want them to eat a hot dog. Right. Well,
I guess they're they don't they don't do
pork, right? So, okay. Eat a I don't
know. Can I eat hamburger? Right.
Hamburger or a steak or something. Yes.
Come and be and be part Come and enjoy
America. We will come over there and
enjoy Turkey. I think this is really
normal. It is. So if you go to Turkey,
it's common practice to shave your head
bald. Okay, let's go ahead and relax
there. Right. So uh this is the new Oh
my god. Is this based? Yeah. Henry
Kissinger. Oh boy. And your ideological
pro uh profile. Troskyist communism. Oh
my god. National conservatism. You're
goddamn right. Left-w leaning. I do feel
like this one is definitely a lot, bro.
Oh man, that is crazy.
Benjamin Netanyahu.
Wow. And this is the same one I just
did, right? Example, result fascism.
Okay. Yeah. And uh Wow. Post yours to X.
And uh yeah, crazy compatibility. Yeah,
I know. I mean, this is just really
insane. And I'm looking at some of these
other people here, too. Updated slop.
Let's see over here. I decided I wanted
to take my political test. It's pretty
damn accurate. Alt light. I mean again
these people like I gave the fact that I
landed both the German Empire and the
Holy Roman Empire man
this person seems like they could be an
OG right yeah and uh it's already got me
updated technocracy Oenheimer oh boy neo
authoritarian neoliberal penish
all right and uh oh my god
wow Wow.
Figure closest to you, Theodore
Roosevelt. Oh, mine was on that was on
my list, too.
Oh my god.
Well, guys, uh, post attack and says,
"I'm feeling cute." I mean,
I don't I I I feel like really
I I I feel like this pretty much is I
mean, that's about right.
Yeah. I mean, you're basically a
liberal. Yeah, I'm pretty basic. I'm I'm
basically a liberal, guys.
Yeah, this is this is pretty much it.
Yeah, this is what I've been trying to
tell everybody.
And
post it. I'm not posting this. It's
going to get posted. I'm just about
right. You know what? Let's not do that
one. How about that? See what Pete
Haggess said about the new military.
He's a watcher. No, I I'll pull it up in
a minute. Let me find it. So,
bro, these mods are getting crazy with
AI. Is this the with uh
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
I'll have to look at that.
You're a gay conservative.
Thanks, man. I appreciate it. Yeah,
that's that's exactly what I wanted to
be. And uh wow, it's going to happen
anyways. Yeah, this is this is going on
Twitter no matter what. I do think that
so the way that I imagine myself,
I think that I am more socially
progressive, but as I've gotten older, I
have become less socially progressive
because I've seen the people that aren't
so that are that are socially
progressive allow society to decay.
And I think that like like it's it's
kind of like what I was saying before
about that ketamine soup kitchen that
all of those retards were were part of
with uh with Cornell University.
My goal isn't to put all the men in jail
or to put the women in jail.
They all go to jail.
All of them. Every We're done with this.
We're t No. No. I don't want to hear it.
No. Absolutely not. I'm tired of it. I'm
done. I'm tired. Yes, exactly. Progress
for progress's sake. Yes, exactly. A
ketamine soup kitchen. Yeah, I thought
that was a pretty accurate analysis,
right? So, uh anyway, closest country to
me is Poland. I'd be like, Poland? Oh,
that that's pretty good. That's not so
bad. So, um yeah, I guess this is uh
this is the way that Okay. Cover the
Cornell story. I already talked about
it. I had a pretty controversial take on
it. I did. And I'm not sorry. And uh if
everyone went to jail except me, only
half the crime in the world. Okay. Um so
yeah, let me go. I got Poland as well. I
mean, I just think this is crazy, man.
It really is. Holy
Steve Bannon, too. That's nuts. Wow. I
uh
man,
that's insane.
What a what a good what a good one. What
a really really good one. I mean, this
was really This is a really good This is
a really good test. I love By the way, I
love taking tests like this. I do like I
I I love taking Why did I not get the
same thing that they did? Uh like the
same layout. And uh yeah, I I have no
idea.
And uh link the test again. Yeah, I'll
link you guys the test. Why not? Give me
one second. I'll go ahead and put it in
chat.
There it is. And so mobile probably.
Yeah. I mean, we have a lot of people
watching, so like obviously it might
mess up the website, so you guys might
need to wait a little bit longer. Neo
values. Oh, what is the rest of this? No
exact match. Left-wing pragmaticism. Oh
god. Oh no. Not another one of these
people. Uh, canes. Really? Yes. And by
the way, I want to say that am I happy
and do I feel satisfied with the result
of this?
Abso lutely I do.
I feel totally vindicated.
I feel like this proves that I've been
right about everything.
It does. It proves that I've been right
about everything uh the whole time. It's
good to hear. Yes, exactly.
God damn it. I'm 92% Araco as well. No.
And I I know that, you know, some people
might not see it the way that I see it,
but that's the way I look at. Is this
astrology for men? Yeah. Uh like polit
politics is astrology for men.
I think that's actually a really good
way to say